Don't you want a little payback?
I do! I have to!
Surprise me when I wake up!
Let's do a wake-up surprise!
I'm nervous!
Good morning!
It's 5:02.
I'd like to call Yumeka-chan now.
Hello, Yumeka-chan.
Can I ask you to open the room?
Sorry.
Excuse me.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
I'm coming.
Oh, my God.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Get lots of sleep when you can.
Sleep when you can.
You're lying.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's no big deal, if you're awake.
You're quitting.
I am.
You're cute.
Oh! That's great!
I can't get through the door.
Oh, my gosh!
Isn't it perfect?
Like 6:30 this morning.
It's 6:40. I'm going to surprise Nai-Nai today.
I'm going to do it as payback for something he said to me 3 times.
Oh, no! Worst!
I hate it! Worst!
Ayaa! Worst!
Worst!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
What do you mean?
No, no, no, no, no.
200 minutes.
What?
Wait, just take 20 minutes.
You're not with me, are you?
What?
That's great.
What? Really?
Really?
I thought for sure we made it.
Oh, man.
I was going so fast.
He got me.
Well, I don't know what I'm gonna do.
I'm going home already motivated.
I'm waiting to spend an hour tomorrow morning putting my hair up.
I'm not here, or the insta-live talk.
I'm already done with the last of it. See?
You're not getting up. I've been here the whole time.
I'll be right here, watching.
I'm looking forward to it.
Wait, are you serious?
You mean it starts today? Today?
It's a repeat of the other one.
I just want it to be this big, and I just want it to fall.
Is it falling?
Oh, my God.
These people are unbelievable.
Oh, shit, there's two cameras.
Oh, my God.
I don't feel well.
I'm so bad.
I've been in bed for like 10 minutes when I wake up.
Who can't get up
Why is this person sleeping with me?
Wake up!
Hurry up, you idiot!
No, I can't. I'm not supposed to.
Is that what you want?
I was looking forward to it.
I went to bed looking forward to it.
It's wake-up time. I always wake up in my sleep.
Geez.
That feels good.
Shut up, really.
Shut up, you're such a jerk.
It doesn't feel good.
Look at the no.
Oh, really?
What's the theme of the fashion show?
What?
That's crazy. I can't believe it.
It's definitely a compliment.
I think I'd like to read the questionnaire that Yumika just wrote.
What? Why?
Why?
It's not funny, because... TOWERECON, no, no, it's not funny.
The questionnaire I wrote to Mr. Hiroshima Atten at Towercon.
That's right.
That's right!
Yes, that's right!
Hiroshima Atten-san!
I wrote it very seriously.
What is today's fashion theme?
I thought it was funny, I thought it was funny.
Since it was Delicious, I decided to wear a dress with a big collar, like a maid's.
It's embarrassing.
Okay, the next thing that's been bothering me lately is...
What did I write?
These questions.
I've gotten into the habit of stretching the bridge of my nose all over people!
I don't care. I don't care. I'm sorry.
What does that mean?
It's kind of a habit to do it like this.
It's a habit. Lately, yeah. Yeah, yeah.
You do it all the time.
It's so much of a habit, my nickname in middle school was Voldemort.
I hate pranks like this. What kind of pranks?
Beatboxing in the middle of a conversation.
Thank you very much for your answers.
I look forward to working with you again today.
So, this was a survey from TOWERECO, Hiroshima store!
It's absolutely a lie. It's absolutely a lie.
It's absolutely a lie.
It's so tiny!
It's a little chi-chi, the mastermind behind all this.
Thank you very much.
Delicious.
Are they getting along?
Have I had a drink?
You didn't, did you?
You haven't had a drink, have you?
No, I didn't.
Wow, look how close the camera is again.
That's funny.
The moment this camera rolls.
I know what I'm going to find.
Behind you.
What's starting...
It's almost over.
I'm almost done.
Just a little more
Hello.
I'm about to get Mr. Liane's
I'm going to replace her Bluetooth earphones
I'm going to replace them with shimeji mushrooms.
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
Good, good, good, good, good, good.
My hair is coming out so much.
He's smiling so much.They are laughing so much.
This is good.
I was going to do the same haircut and dance as fast as I could,
But I failed due to various reasons.
That's how it all started.
Yes, that's right. I'm looking forward to the new EP.
I'm looking forward to the new EP.
I'm into listening to music with various earphones,
I would like to know what kind of earphones you guys use,
I'd love to know what kind of earphones you guys are using before the EP is released.
I'd love to know what kind of earphones you guys are using before the EP comes out.
I use Soundcore.
Really. Same thing.
But I don't know if it's good or bad. I'm not sure if it's good or bad.
Let me see what's inside.
Oh, no. I'm embarrassed.
Why not?
Why don't you just show me one of them in a talk?
No, I can't. No, I can't.
Please. Please, for the rest of my life.
Please for the rest of my life.
Surprise?
I'm scared.
It's not a surprise.
What is it?
What are you...
Hey, what are you doing?
Who did this? Look!
Can you see it? Take a picture, take a picture. Take a picture.
What if he didn't want to show it like that?
Who did this? I'm serious.
No, it's not... two days, I don't know what this means.
What is this?
What was that?
Shimeji?
Why? That's unusual.
They use shimeji mushrooms.
Look at the inside.
I don't have any.
I thought they were dirty, but they're not shimeji.
I don't get it anymore. What's this?
I'll leave it here for a while.
Next.
Oh, my gosh. I mean, isn't this it?
Can I ask the next question?
What do you value in life as a human being?
Sound quality? Shimeji.
Which one do you put in? This one. This one?
Wait a minute. I'm not using it.
Which one do you put in? This one. This one, right?
You're putting it in this way?
Isn't it Frankenstein style? This way.
I guess it was a reverse surprise this morning.
I thought I could finally get back at him, but then he started dancing the Soran Bush.
I thought I was going to punch him in the face.
Was it a prank?
I think it was malicious, malicious.
New SPC member is leaving!
Wow!
You came all the way to Osaka?
Thanks for coming.
Seriously?
Thank you so much!
I came from Tokyo.
Wow!
Who's who?
Who's that?
You're bringing him in?
We're bringing in new talent.
I'm so glad.
They're here!
A new member.
I'm Chankoy, a new member.
I'm looking forward to working with you starting today.
Nice to meet you.
I liked what you liked.
That's right, that's right. I was hoping to get used to it.
Skip the training camp.
Honors student!
That's great!
Let's start working together today.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Yay!
I have to go home.
Kati, may I?
I have a cat at home.
It's time to feed him.
Tickets for the bullet train?
I'm in trouble.
You don't have to stay at home.
Okawa Sensei said he'd turn it.
He said he'll be the signalman.
Yes, he said I'd do it.
But I have to go home.
I knew it...
No, no, no, no!
Allowing the cat...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Shinkansen!
You asked for it.
Can you change the time?
Yes, I can.
Aah!
Thanks for your help.
You can't leave by yourself.
I'm going home. The cat's waiting for me, Mr. Tule.
It's a big embarrassment, this whole morning.
You're happy, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
I can already tell.
Like, "Oh, I get it.
That's why you're waiting for the camera.
I'm starting to get it.
Wow, that makes me happy.
Wow.
I'm so glad you're here.
Come here, please.
I'm so happy!
Please take a look at this one too.
Nice to meet you today.
I hope you can remember me.
We are the same members.
In katakana, we are Yumekanaukana Hatena.
I'm Yumekanaukana.
I'm a member.
I'm a member! I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm a member of this group.
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy for you, Governor.
That's great! Thank you so much!
Welcome back.
Thank you very much.
Good, good, good.
Already, leaving Shibuya
This is the must town!
Yes, it is
We've been all over this country
What's in the bag?
I don't really know what's in our bags.
I'd like to introduce it to you.
I'm sure you're all curious about it.
Don't you?
Of course you do.
Really?
What's in your bag?
And you didn't bring anything interesting.And you didn't bring anything interesting at all.
So all of a sudden, you were like, "Let's do something.
Let's take a look at Yumeka's.
What's this? This dress.
What? Did you put that in here? I'm scared.
I'm scared.
What is this?
It's so energetic.
Who did this?
This is the turmeric.
I'm scared.
One bottle of this for a man's confidence and fulfillment.
You've always made your energy from drinks, haven't you?
What? No? Really.
I showed you what's in my bag today.
Who put it in there?
What? This.
See? That's what I'm talking about.
It's all about a man's confidence and contentment, isn't it?
Yeah, that's right.
Who put this in there? Really.
I don't trust anyone.
I'm doing my best today because it's my last.
I can't stop laughing. I can't stop laughing.
It's so gross, but it's so funny.
But you were really happy, weren't you?
I'm not!
Are you the one who was hit on?
That's right!
No, no, no!
Did you hear it from my face?
He called me!
You're arguing with me?
No, I was listening with your face the whole time.
Time!
A prank.
Right!
Like graffiti.
Yes!
So, people and us were pranked.
Oh, yeah.
People who got pranked!
Gentlemen!
Yes!
Oh, no!
Not us!
You know what, you guys don't know, do you?
You don't know what happened behind the scenes.
Yes, the members were pranked too.
Rion got pranked a lot.
Oh, me too!
What?
No!
Who?
No! There's someone behind this!
You've been pranked!
He's definitely behind this!
He's scary too!
No, no, no, no, I...
I'm...
I'm being eaten by bugs.
It's the same thing! It's the same thing!
Same thing! It's the same thing!
I'm being eaten by bugs.
No, no, no, it's the last one, really.
It's the last one, really.
Seino!
Thank you very much!
Congratulations!
by H.
I don't know if I can say
But when it comes to these ears
You'll believe me.
Beyond you... that's what matters now.
I'm looking at the camera.
No, I don't know what you're doing.
I don't know what to do.
What?
Who's that?
Which one is the Yumekan with cheese?
It's bad. It's really bad.
Who did it?
What? Who did it?
Who? Who?
Who did it?
Who?
I did it.
What?
It was me.
But I'm one of them.
What? Really?
Really? Really? Really?
I think we're on the same side.
That's him.
It's me.
What? Who did it?
So there was someone else on the team.
That's right.
That makes sense.
You said there'd be a "delirious" reward, so I'm just...
I'm finally feeling refreshed.
That's it... we can say hi.
Let's do this.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
Have a good day. Watch again.
It's the end. It's the end.
It's the last time.
What was the best part?
What did you like best?
The quality.
Quality?
Oh, I meant the letter.
Yeah, I know, right?
I had a letter done,
To the Prime Minister's son.
But it's pretty well written, isn't it?
Yes, I did. I wrote the whole thing.
I was quite moved.
I liked the letter.
Bye bye.
It was fun.
And I was in so much trouble.
But their reaction was really troubling.
I was troubled too.
I was troubled.
I think you were able to do what you wanted to do when you were a child.
I was thinking, "Hey, you know, you should bring it to Ginga,
Then you can do it like this. What if I say bye-bye?
That's the way it is,
I'm always frustrated with the two of them,
No, I'm just so frustrated.
I'm frustrated too.
I got it, and then you just did it.
It feels good.
Please beat the shit out of me when I get home.
I'll insulate myself.
That was fun, wasn't it?
It was fun. Thank you very much.
Please take care of me.
I thought people get psychotic when they get so naughty.
My favorite.It's my favorite.
But I laughed a lot when I saw the glue in the bullet train ticket.
That was good.
I mean, that was the scariest thing I've ever seen.
I don't know.
Was that part of the setup already?
Yeah.
The three of us were talking about where to go.
Really? I wonder if they even noticed it at all.
I thought everyone would just say "thank you" and leave.
I thought everyone was going to say "thank you" and leave,
But suddenly everyone started singing.
I thought it was a surprise.
I thought that everyone's spirit of service was amazing.
I just said, "Wow!
That was amazing.
Then the "A" thing started, and I was surprised.
I was surprised. I thought they were going to do it already.
Then, I didn't understand what was going on, and I thought I was being set up.
He looked so confused.
I didn't know what was going on and we passed each other.
No, my eyes met Leon's.
I thought he was doing this.
It was fun.
Really?
You're getting chills, aren't you?
Oh, really.
Look forward to seeing you next time.
Bye-bye.
I'm already a misanthrope.
It was hard, wasn't it? The bitterness in our hearts.
Because when I called Yamada at 5 in the morning,
When I called Yamada-chan at 5:00 a.m., my heart ached.
I was naked in my hotel pajamas,
I felt like I was floating,
Who was it?
I called her in my sleep,
Naked what? Like, what?
Why are you sleeping?
Oh, my God! That's disgusting!